Guide to the Duke University Playbills collection, 1933-1970 UA.31.07.0800
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Playbills collection
1933-1970
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University
UA.31.07.0800
1.25 Linear Feet
Playbills from numerous events held in Page Auditorium between 1933-1970. Includes musical and theatrical events, such as productions by Duke Player, recitals, symphonic performances, and solo singers.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Provenance
Transfer.
Collection Overview
Playbills from numerous events held in Page Auditorium between 1933-1970. Includes musical and theatrical events, such as productions by Duke Player, recitals, symphonic performances, and solo singers.
Related Materials
Department of Theater Studies Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke Players Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Department of Music Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Theater programs; Duke University; Duke University. Duke Players
- Page Auditorium, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Page Auditorium: North Carolina Symphony Society, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Duke University Chapel, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Page Auditorium, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Page Auditorium, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Page Auditorium, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Page Auditorium, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Page Auditorium, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Page Auditorium, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Page Auditorium, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Page Auditorium, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Page Auditorium, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Page Auditorium, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Page Auditorium, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Page Auditorium, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Page Auditorium, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Branson Hall, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Page Auditorium, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Page Auditorium: Miscellaneous, 1929-1951 & undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Page Auditorium, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Branson Hall, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Page Auditorium, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Branson Hall, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Page Auditorium, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Branson Hall, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Page Auditorium, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Branson Hall, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Music Room, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Branson Hall, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Page Auditorium, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Branson Hall, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Page Auditorium, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Branson Hall, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Page Auditorium, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Branson Hall, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Page Auditorium, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Page Auditorium, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Branson Hall, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Branson Hall, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Page Auditorium, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Page Auditorium, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Page Auditorium, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Page Auditorium, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Page Auditorium, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Indoor Stadium, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Branson Hall, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Page Auditorium, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Indoor Stadium, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Page Auditorium, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Indoor Stadium, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Page Auditorium, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Indoor Stadium, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Branson Hall, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Page Auditorium, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Indoor Stadium, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Page Auditorium, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Duke University Union, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)